A Guide to the Papers of Paul Saunier, Jr., 1960-1972
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of Paul Saunier, Jr. 1960-1972
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-4/2/10.701
This collection consists of 17 cubic boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Stored off-site. Users must request boxes 48 hours in advance of desired use. Neither drop-in nor next-day requests can be fulfilled. For additional information, contact Special Collections.
Acquisition Information
This collection was an archival transfer to the University Library, 1974 January 22 and August 20.
Biographical/Historical Information
Paul Saunier, Jr. served the University in a variety of positions during President Shannon=s tenure as President. The Assistant to the President for University Relations and Development was a policy advising position for public relations and the coordination of fund raising organizations at the university. Mr. Saunier held the position from 1960 until the position terminated in the spring of 1967. His primary task in this role was to increase the outward flow of information and the inward flow of intellectual, moral, and financial support which the University needed in order to increase the quality and quantity of its programs. In 1967 the position of Assistant to the President for University Relations and Development was abolished. The assistant's duties were split between the new Director of Development and Public Affairs and the Director of University Relations, a position which was filled by Mr. Saunier. In 1971 Mr. Saunier's title became Director of University Community Relations, a title which more clearly represented the functions of his office as they had evolved over a five-year period. The position of Director of University Community Relations was discontinued in June 1972.
Scope and Content
This collection consists of the Papers of Paul Saunier, Jr.
Organization
The original manuscript classification numbers for this collection are listed in parenthesis after the new Record Group Numbers:
RG-4/2/10.701 (7306-g); RG-4/2/10.751 (7306-I); RG-4/2/10.741 (9248-f).
All folders are inter-filed with RG-4/2/10.701. Group II consists entirely of RG-4/2/10.741. For more information, please see University Archives Control Folder RG-4/2.
Contents List
- GROUP I: Assistant to the President for University Relations & Development
  - Correspondence, Misc. A-Z 1962-1964, 4 folders. (Box 1)
    restrictions.
  - Adams, Hazel Ruth-Martinsville 1962-1963 (Box 1)
    see also equal opportunity.
  - Admissions [1961-1968] (Box 1)
    restricted.
  - Admissions Report 1964, [1966] (Box 1)
  - Alderman Library 1961-1967, 3 folders. (Box 1)
  - All-Virginia High School Bands [1961-1964] (Box 1)
  - Alumni [1966] (Box 1)
  - Alumni Association 1960-1965, 4 folders. (Box 1)
  - Alumni Day [1963-1964] (Box 1)
  - Alumni Fund 1959-1965, 3 folders. (Box 2)
  - Alumni Fund Mailing Times [1965] (Box 2)
  - Alumni Fund-"Prospects" 1963 (Box 2)
  - Alumni News [1964-1965] (Box 2)
  - Alumni Seminars 1961 (Box 2)
  - Alumni Weekend [1962-1965] (Box 2)
  - American Council on Education [1963-1966] (Box 2)
  - American Program Bureau [1960] (Box 2)
    TV Celebrities.
  - Appropriations [1966] (Box 2)
  - Architecture, School of [1961-1968] (Box 2)
  - Arts & Sciences, College of [1961-1968], 2 folders. (Box 2)
  - Arts & Sciences, Graduate School 1962-1968, 2 folders. (Box 2)
  - Association of State Universities & Land Grant Colleges [1963-1969], 5 folders. (Box 2)
  - Astronomy 1961-1968 (Box 2)
  - Athletics, Department of [1961-1968], 3 folders. (Box 2)
  - ATM-Z-A Manual Air Traffic Control Proced. [1961-1962] (Box 2)
  - Band Day [1964-1966] (Box 2)
  - Beechcraft 1964 (Box 2)
  - Berkley, F.L. [1963-1968] (Box 2)
  - Blandy Experimental Farm [1965] (Box 3)
  - Board of Visitors [1961-1966] (Box 3)
  - Bomb Threats [1967] (Box 3)
  - Lea Booth [1960-1965] (Box 3)
  - Boroff 1964 (Box 3)
  - Branch Colleges Abandonment of Eastern Shore Branch and Patrick Henry College [1962-1972] (Box 3)
  - Branch Colleges Development: Eastern Shore Branch [1962-1972], 3 folders. (Box 3)
  - Branch Colleges Development: George Mason College [1962-1972], 2 folders. (Box 3)
    see also George Mason.
  - Branch Colleges Lynchburg [1966] (Box 3)
  - Branch Colleges Miscellaneous [1966] (Box 3)
    see also Community College, Martinsville, Mary Mount.
  - Branch Colleges Roanoke Branch [1962-1972], 2 folders. (Box 3)
    see also Roanoke-Community College.
  - Branch Colleges Sites for Patrick Henry College [1965-1966] (Box 3)
  - Budget Information [1962-1966] (Box 3)
  - Building Projects 1962 (Box 3)
  - Business Administration, Graduate School of 1960-1968, 3 folders. (Box 3)
  - Business-Topics 1961-1965, 2 folders. (Box 4)
  - Cabell Chair [1967-1968] (Box 4)
  - (Box 4)
  - Calendar and Scheduling 1962-1965, 2 folders. (Box 4)
  - Calendar and Scheduling Committee 1968 (Box 4)
  - Calendar Events Committee [1964-1968] (Box 4)
  - Capital Outlay [1966-1974] (Box 4)
  - Car Regulations 1963 (Box 4)
  - Center for Advanced Studies in Sciences 1966-1967 (Box 4)
  - Charlottesville-200th Anniversary 1962, 2 folders. (Box 4)
  - Chase-Cheatham Correspondence [1966] (Box 4)
  - Chattanooga Correspondence 1962-1964 (Box 4)
  - Child & Family Service [1961-1966], 2 folders. (Box 4)
  - Civil Defense 1961-1962 (Box 4)
  - Civil War Centennial 1961 (Box 4)
  - Commission on State and Local Revenues and Expenditures and Related Matters 1963 (Box 4)
  - Commonwealth Day 1961-1968, 6 folders. (Box 4)
  - Community College Clinch Valley College [1961-1965] (Box 4)
    see also Branch Colleges.
  - Community College Covington 1961 (Box 4)
  - Community Relations [1964-1966] (Box 4)
  - Computer Center 1963 (Box 4)
  - Conner, James R. 1963-1965 (Box 4)
  - Copeley Hill Nursery-Kindergarten 1966-1967 (Box 5)
  - Corks and Curls 1962 (Box 5)
  - Council for Financial Aid to Education [1961] (Box 5)
  - Cyclotron 1962-1963 (Box 5)
  - Deans and Departments Heads [1966-1968] (Box 5)
  - Delmarva Business Service [1965-1966] (Box 5)
  - Demolay 1962 (Box 5)
  - Development Organization 1961 (Box 5)
  - Drinking [1961-1966] (Box 5)
  - Editorial Writers [n.d.] (Box 5)
  - Educational Communication Center 1961-1965 (Box 5)
  - Educational Research 1963 (Box 5)
  - Educational Television 1961-1967, 4 folders. (Box 5)
  - Engineering, School of [1961-1968] (Box 5)
  - Engineering Foundation 1961 (Box 5)
  - Engineering Open House 1961 (Box 5)
  - Equal Employment Opportunity-Compliance [1965] (Box 5)
  - Equal Opportunity / Discrimination: Non-discrimination Regulations 1966 (Box 5)
  - EWA Tour 1967 (Box 5)
  - Faculty 1965-1967, 2 folders. (Box 5)
  - Faculty of Arts & Sciences 1962-1968 (Box 5)
  - Faculty Salaries [1961-64], 2 folders. (Box 5)
  - William Faulkner 1962 (Box 5)
  - William Faulkner House 1963-1965 (Box 5)
  - Finals 1961-1966 (Box 5)
  - Fine Arts 1963-1968 (Box 5)
  - Fine Arts Calendar [1964-1965] (Box 5)
  - Football Schedule 1961-1962, 2 folders. (Box 5)
  - Football Tickets: Judge Advocates General's School [1966] (Box 5)
  - Foreign Student Advisor 1965-1968 (Box 5)
  - Founder's Day [1961-1966] (Box 5)
  - Friends Of The Library [1962-1966] (Box 5)
  - Fundraising [1965-1966] (Box 6)
  - Fundraising: Coordinated Fund [1963-1964] (Box 6)
  - Fundraising Organizations [1960-64], 2 folders. (Box 6)
  - General Assembly 1966 (Box 6)
  - General Electric College Bowl 1962-1963 (Box 6)
  - General Studies, School of 1961-1968, 2 folders. (Box 6)
  - George Mason, Community College 1960-1966, 2 folders. (Box 6)
  - Gifts and Grants 1962-1965, 6 folders. (Box 6)
  - Giving, Miscellaneous. [1964-1965] (Box 6)
  - Graduate Studies Project 1966 (Box 7)
  - Gifted and Talented Children 1963 (Box 7)
  - Graphics, Dept. of 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - Green Bank Scientists 1964 (Box 7)
  - GSBA Tenth Anniversary Committee 1965 (Box 7)
  - Guide Service 1963-1965 (Box 7)
  - Hazing 1963 (Box 7)
  - Henry Clay Hofheimer, II [1960-1964] (Box 7)
  - High School Senior Day [1962-1964] (Box 7)
  - Highway Safety 1963 (Box 7)
  - Hobbs, Mr. William A. [1966-1968] (Box 7)
  - Holiday Magazine 1961 (Box 7)
  - Housing [1964-1966] (Box 7)
  - Housing, Married Student 1965 (Box 7)
  - Hospital Dedication 1961 (Box 7)
  - Hospital Rape Case-Davis Ward 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Humphries, Ralph 1962-1965 (Box 7)
  - Industrial Research and Development Center, School of Engineering 1965 (Box 7)
  - Industrial Commission [1961-66] (Box 7)
  - Industrial Development [1962-1966], 2 folders. (Box 7)
  - Information Coordinating Board 1961-1965 (Box 7)
  - Insurance Plans 1961-1962 (Box 7)
  - Information Service 1961-1968, 3 folders. (Box 7)
  - Information Service Program News and Work In Progress [1965-1966] (Box 7)
  - James River Basin Association 1962-1963 (Box 7)
  - Jefferson Chapter Virginia Council on Human Religion 1965-1966 (Box 7)
  - John Randolph Society: Speakers [1963] (Box 7)
    see also Nazis, Speaker Ban Law, Speakers--Civil Rights.
  - July 4th 1963 (Box 7)
    Monticello.
  - Kennedy, John F. [1960] (Box 7)
  - Kennedy, Ted 1962 (Box 7)
  - King Jr., Martin Luther 1963 (Box 7)
  - Knox Turnball Financial Planning & Deferred Gift Program [1966] (Box 7)
  - Law, School of 1964-1968, 2 folders. (Box 8)
  - Law Day 1964-1965 (Box 8)
  - Local Contacts 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Long Range Planning 1960-1961 (Box 8)
  - Lynchburg Foundry Company 1966 (Box 8)
    The Iron Worker.
  - Community College, Martinsville [1962-1966], 2 folders. (Box 8)
  - Mary Mount College 1966 (Box 8)
  - Master Site Plan 1965-1972, 2 folders. (Box 8)
  - McCall's 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Medical School In Tidewater Area [1963-1966] (Box 8)
  - Memorial Gymnasium 1962 (Box 8)
  - Sir Robert Menzies [1966-1967] (Box 8)
  - Minneapolis-Honeywell Regulator Co.-CW Hagerman 1961 (Box 8)
  - Minor, C. Venable 1965-1967 (Box 8)
  - Narcotics Violation [n.d.] (Box 8)
  - National Football Foundation Hall of Fame-Robert K. Gooch 1961 (Box 8)
  - Nazis & Fascists [1962-1963], see also John Randolph Society, Speaker Ban Law, Speakers--Civil Rights. (Box 8)
    see also John Randolph Society, Speaker Ban Law, Speakers--Civil Rights.
  - Newcomb Hall [1963-1968] (Box 8)
  - News Bureau Ideas 1961 (Box 8)
  - Newspaper Clippings [1961-1964] (Box 8)
  - Newspapers [1960-1968], 3 folders. (Box 8)
  - Nitti Case 1966-1967 (Box 8)
  - Norfolk Sales Tax 1964 (Box 8)
  - Oak Ridge 1962 (Box 8)
  - Office Equipment 1961-1966 (Box 8)
  - Organization Charts [1965] (Box 8)
  - Out of State Students [1964] (Box 8)
  - Pardue Case 1961 (Box 8)
  - Parking [1962-1966] (Box 8)
  - Personnel [1963-1966] (Box 8)
  - Personnel Practices [1965-1966] (Box 8)
  - Photographic Services [1962-1965] (Box 8)
  - Political Leaders [1960-1968], 6 folders. (Box 9)
  - Bureau of Population & Economic Research [1964-1968] (Box 9)
  - President's Box 1964 (Box 9)
  - Prints: includes Color Enlargement [1962] (Box 9)
  - Publications [1961-1965] (Box 9)
  - Publications, UVA [n.d.] (Box 9)
  - Public Relations [1961-1966] (Box 9)
  - Publish or Perish 1967 (Box 9)
  - Radio-TV 1960-1964, 2 folders. (Box 9)
  - Walter Reed-Yellow Fever Col. [1965-1967] (Box 9)
  - Registrar [1963-1968] (Box 9)
  - Religious Affairs [1963-1966] (Box 9)
  - Re-organization, Information Service 1961 (Box 9)
  - Requisitions: Inter-Departmental Invoices [1964-1968], 2 folders. (Box 9)
  - Requisitions: Invoices [1964-1968], 2 folders. (Box 10)
  - Requisitions: Travel Vouchers [1964-1968] (Box 10)
  - Riots 1961 (Box 10)
  - Roanoke-Community College [1961-1962], 2 folders. (Box 10)
  - Rotary Club, Program Committee [n.d.] (Box 10)
  - Rotunda Dance [1965-1968] (Box 10)
  - Runk, B.F.D. [1965-1968] (Box 10)
  - Saunier, Nes [1960-1964] (Box 10)
  - Saunier, Paul [1962-1966], 2 folders. (Box 10)
    Personal.
  - Saunier's Speaking Engagements [1962-1966] (Box 10)
  - Scholarships [1961-1966] (Box 10)
  - Scholarships, Loans, Grants 1966 (Box 10)
  - Science Development Grant [1965-1968] (Box 10)
  - Selective Service [1966-1969] (Box 10)
  - Sesquicentennial Celebration [1967-1969], 3 folders. (Box 10)
  - Shannon, Mr. [1960-1968], 1-3 of 6 folders. (Box 10)
  - Shannon, Mr. [1960-1968], 4-6 of 6 folders. (Box 11)
  - Speaker Ban Law-clippings [1965] (Box 11)
    see also John Randolph Society.
  - Speakers-Civil Rights [1965] (Box 11)
  - State Council of Higher Education [1961-1965] (Box 11)
  - Southern Regional Education Board [1967-1968], 2 folders. (Box 11)
  - SREB-Gen. [1961-1966], 2 folders. (Box 11)
  - Southern Regional Science Seminar [1960-1961] (Box 11)
  - SQUID 1961 (Box 11)
  - Student Council [1965-1968] (Box 11)
  - Students for Social Action [n.d.] (Box 11)
  - Sturman, John F. - UVA Administration Correspondence [1965-1967] (Box 11)
  - Sturman, John F. - Misc. Newsletters [1965-1967] (Box 11)
  - Sturman, John F. - Drake Correspondence [1965-1967] (Box 11)
  - Summer School [1964-1967] (Box 11)
  - Tampa 1961 (Box 11)
  - Textbooks 1967 (Box 11)
  - TIAA Exhibit 1961 (Box 11)
  - T.J. Center 1961 (Box 11)
  - Thomas Jefferson Council-Churchill [1965] (Box 11)
  - Thomas Jefferson Society [1964] (Box 11)
  - Tornado-Richmond [1951] (Box 12)
  - Traffic Control Reports 1960-1964 (Box 12)
  - Travel 1960 (Box 12)
  - Turner, Terry Mr. & Mrs. [1968] (Box 12)
  - United Givers Fund [1963-1965] (Box 12)
  - University 1962-1965 (Box 12)
  - University Band 1965 (Box 12)
  - University Club [1965-1966] (Box 12)
  - University Education Extension Bill 1962 (Box 12)
  - University of Washington Calendar of Events [1965] (Box 12)
  - University Press of Virginia [1963-1967], 2 folders. (Box 12)
  - University Printing Order [1961-1963] (Box 12)
  - University Relations & Development, Bi-Monthly Summary 1962 (Box 12)
  - University Reports 1961-1966, 6 folders. (Box 12)
  - University Reports-Hospital [1967-1968] (Box 12)
  - University Theatre 1961 (Box 12)
  - University Topics 1961-1963 (Box 12)
  - Uva Alumni Medical Association. [n.d.] (Box 12)
  - Uva Medical Alumni Association. [1962-1965] (Box 12)
  - Va. Associated Research Center [1963-1965] (Box 12)
  - Va. Cultural Development Study Commission [1967] (Box 12)
  - Virginia Electric and Power Co. 1961-1962 (Box 12)
  - Virginia Flag 1964 (Box 12)
  - Virginia Polytechnical Institute [1963-1969] (Box 12)
  - Virginia Press Association [1961-1964] (Box 12)
  - Virginia Sports Broadcasting, Inc. 1961 (Box 12)
  - Vaughan, Mr. [1963-1966] (Box 12)
  - Wilkinson Jr., J. Harvey [1963-1965] (Box 12)
  - William and Mary [1962-1970] (Box 12)
  - Wranek, Mr. Bill 1961-1965 (Box 12)
  - ALL FILES RESTRICTED (Box 13)
- GROUP II: Director of University Relations
  - Admissions-General 1968-1971 (Box 14)
  - Admissions-Admission of Women 1967-1971 (Box 14)
  - Albemarle County Planning Commission 1969 (Box 14)
  - Alderman Library 1968-1972 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Association-General 1965-1971 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Association-Gilbert Sullivan, Director, Alumni Association 1965-1970 (Box 14)
  - Alumni Association-Alumni Fund 1965-1970 (Box 14)
  - Arts and Sciences, College of 1968-1972 (Box 14)
  - A.S.P.O.: American Society of Planning Officials 1970 (Box 14)
  - Astronomy 1968-1971 (Box 14)
  - Athletics, Department of 1968-1972 (Box 14)
  - Birdwood 1971 (Box 14)
  - Board of Visitors 1967-1971 (Box 14)
  - Bookstore Controversy 1967-1970 (Box 14)
  - Buildings and Grounds 1969-1972 (Box 14)
  - Calendar and Scheduling Committee-General 1968-1972, 2 folders. (Box 14)
  - Calendar and Scheduling Committee-Scheduling Subcommittee 1969-1972 (Box 14)
  - Calendar of Events 1970-1971 (Box 14)
  - Capital Outlay Study 1966-1972 (Box 14)
  - Cavalier Daily 1964-1971 (Box 14)
  - Coeducation 1970 (Box 14)
  - Committee on the Future of the University 1966-1971 (Box 14)
  - Commonwealth Day 1969 (Box 14)
  - Weldon Cooper-Director, Institute of Government 1969-1971 (Box 14)
  - Community Colleges-General 1962-1968 (Box 14)
  - Community Colleges-Community College Committee Meetings 1962-1967 (Box 14)
  - Community Colleges-Eastern Shore Branch-Wallops Station 1964-1970, 2 folders. (Box 14)
  - Community Colleges-George Mason College 1964-1970, 2 folders. (Box 14)
  - Community Colleges-Lynchburg 1961-1967 (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges-Madison 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges-Manassas 1966 (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges-Northern Virginia 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges-Patrick Henry College 1966-1969 (Box 15)
    Martinsville.
  - Community Colleges-Roanoke 1964-1966, 2 folders. (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges-Roanoke Center 1967 (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges-Clinch Valley College 1967-1970 (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges-Longwood College 1967-1969 (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges-Mary Washington College 1962-1969 (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges-R.P.I. 1967 (Box 15)
  - Community Colleges-Virginia Military Institute 1967-1970 (Box 15)
  - Complaints 1961-1971 (Box 15)
  - Concert Coordinating Committee 1971 (Box 15)
  - Crawford, Edwin-Vice President for Public Affairs 1970-1972 (Box 15)
  - Creative Television 1965-1968 (Box 15)
  - Data Processing Center 1970-1972 (Box 15)
  - Deans and Department Heads 1968-1972 (Box 15)
  - Demonstrations 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Development, Director of 1972 (Box 15)
  - Discriminatory Scholarships 1969 (Box 15)
  - Education, School of 1964-1972 (Box 15)
  - Emergency Address Lists 1971 (Box 15)
  - Emergency Procedures 1970-1971 (Box 15)
  - Enrollment Information 1971 (Box 15)
  - Federal Executive Institute 1967-1971 (Box 15)
  - Fellowship of Christian Athletes 1970 (Box 15)
  - Fernandez, Antonio 1970-1971 (Box 15)
    Cuban refugee/pre-medical student. Restricted.
  - Financial Aid to Students 1967-1970 (Box 15)
  - Fund-Raising 1965 (Box 15)
  - General Assembly 1966, 2 folders. (Box 15)
  - George Washington Papers 1968-1970 (Box 15)
  - Glee Club 1968-1969 (Box 15)
  - Gourman Report 1967-1968 (Box 15)
  - Graduate Arts and Sciences 1969-1972 (Box 15)
  - Happiness Party 1971 (Box 15)
  - Hicks, Clarence F.-Attorney General Committee 1966-1969 (Box 15)
  - Hobbs, William A.-Director of Development and Public Affairs 1969 (Box 15)
  - Honor Committee 1966-1971 (Box 15)
  - Housing 1966-1972 (Box 16)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Service 1964-1969, 2 folders. (Box 16)
  - Information Services 1968-1971 (Box 16)
  - Institute of Government 1969-1971 (Box 16)
  - Institutional Analysis, Office of 1967-1972 (Box 16)
  - Jenkins, Paul-Director of Personnel 1967-1969 (Box 16)
  - Jones, Hilary H., III-re football scholarship 1969-1970 (Box 16)
  - Law, School of 1967-1972 (Box 16)
  - Law, School of-Law Day 1966-1970 (Box 16)
  - Martin Luther King Chapter-Virginia Council on Human Relations 1969 (Box 16)
  - Master Site Plan 1967 (Box 16)
  - Medical School Library 1964 (Box 16)
  - Mezey, Michael-Visiting Professor 1970 (Box 16)
  - Middle Atlantic Regional Water Pollution Control Laboratory 1966-1967 (Box 16)
  - Miller Bill 1968 (Box 16)
    H.R. 875.
  - Mountain Lake 1970 (Box 16)
  - Medicine, School of 1965-1972, 2 folders. (Box 16)
  - Middleditch, Leigh B., Jr.-Legal Adviser 1968-1971 (Box 16)
  - Newcomb Hall 1968-1970 (Box 16)
  - November Bond Issue 1968-1969, 2 folders. (Box 16)
  - Nursing, School of 1967-1970 (Box 16)
  - Pep Band 1966 (Box 16)
  - Physics Department 1966-1971 (Box 16)
  - Placement 1969-1971 (Box 16)
  - Planning Department 1962-1970 (Box 16)
  - Provost 1967-1972 (Box 16)
  - President's Office 1968-1972 (Box 16)
  - Public Events Advisory Committee 1968-1969, 4 folders. (Box 16)
  - Racial Identification 1966-1967 (Box 16)
  - Radio Station WTJU 1962-1968 (Box 16)
  - Registrar 1968-1972, 1 of 2. (Box 16)
  - Registrar 1968-1972, 2 of 2. (Box 17)
  - Religious Affairs 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Requisitions 1968-1970 (Box 17)
  - Rotch Committee 1969-1971 (Box 17)
  - Scott, Frederic W. 1967 (Box 17)
  - Security Department 1964-1972 (Box 17)
  - Seven Society 1972 (Box 17)
  - Shea, Vincent-Vice President for Business and Finance 1961-1972 (Box 17)
  - Smith, Ian-Prime Minister of Rhodesia 1967 (Box 17)
  - Student Coalition 1969 (Box 17)
  - Student Council 1969-1971, 2 folders. (Box 17)
  - Student-City Courses 1967 (Box 17)
  - Sponsored Programs 1970-1972 (Box 17)
  - Student Affairs, Dean of 1968-1972 (Box 17)
  - Student Aid and Placement 1961-1966 (Box 17)
  - Student Aid Foundation 1961-1968 (Box 17)
  - Student Council 1972 (Box 17)
  - Student Legal Forum 1971 (Box 17)
  - Summer School 1971-1972 (Box 17)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute 1966-1967 (Box 17)
  - Traffic and Parking Manager 1971-1972 (Box 17)
  - University Airport 1968-1969 (Box 17)
  - University Events 1971 (Box 17)
  - University Hall 1961-1965 (Box 17)
  - University Hospital 1970-1971 (Box 17)
  - University Printing Office 1968-1972 (Box 17)
  - Virginia Easter Seal Society 1970 (Box 17)
  - Virginia Weekly 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - Westmoreland Davis Memorial Foundation 1955-1965 (Box 17)
  - Women, Dean of 1967-1968 (Box 17)
  - Women in Dormitories 1967-1969 (Box 17)
  - Y.M.C.A. 1966-1972 (Box 17)